<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kmahjongg.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">К‑маџонг</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">K‑madžong</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">К‑маџонг</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">K‑madžong</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Mahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKMahjonggxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KMahjongg</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KMahjongg</name>
  <description>
    <p>
      KMahjongg is a fun board game created after the famous oriental game of Mahjong (from Chinese 麻將).
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KMahjongg és un joc de tauler divertit creat a partir del famós jocs oriental Mahjong (del xinès 麻將).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KMahjongg és un joc de tauler divertit creat a partir del famós jocs oriental Mahjong (del xinés 麻將).</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KMahjongg ist ein Brettspiel, das an das berühmte orientalische Spiel Mahjong (Chinesisch: 麻將) angelehnt ist.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το KMahjongg είναι ένα ευχάριστο επιτραπέζιο παιχνίδι με βάση το περίφημο ασιατικό Mahjong (στα Κινεζικά 麻將).</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KMahjongg is a fun board game created after the famous oriental game of Mahjong (from Chinese 麻將).</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KMahjongg es un divertido juego de tablero derivado del famoso juego oriental mahjong (del chino 麻將).</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KMahjongg on hauska lautapeli, joka perustuu tunnettuun itämaiseen Mahjong-peliin (kiinaksi 麻將).</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KMahjongg é un xogo de taboleiro divertido que se creou a partir do famoso xogo oriental Mahjong (do chinés «麻將»).</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KMahjongg is een bordspel naar het voorbeeld van het bekende oosterse spel Mahjongg (van het Chinese 麻將)</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">KMahjongg er eit morosamt brettspel basert på det gamle kinesiske spelet mahjong (frå kinsesik «麻將»).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KMahjongg jest grą planszową stworzoną na wzór słynnej gry orientalnej Mahjong (z chińskiego 麻將).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KMahjongg é um divertido jogo de tabuleiro, criado com base no antigo jogo oriental Mahjong (do Chinês 麻將).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">KMahjongg é um divertido jogo de tabuleiro criado com base no famoso jogo oriental que é o Mahjong (do chinês 麻將).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KMahjongg je zábavná dosková hra vytvorená podľa známej orientálnej hry Mahjong (z čínštiny 麻將).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KMahjongg je zabavna namizna igra, ki je bila ustvarjena po vzoru slavne bližnjevzhodne igre imenovane Mahjong (iz kitajskega imena 麻將).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">К‑маџонг је забавна игра на табли заснована на чувеној оријенталној игри маџонг (од кинеског 麻將).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">K‑madžong je zabavna igra na tabli zasnovana na čuvenoj orijentalnoj igri madžong (od kineskog 麻將).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">К‑маџонг је забавна игра на табли заснована на чувеној оријенталној игри маџонг (од кинеског 麻將).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">K‑madžong je zabavna igra na tabli zasnovana na čuvenoj orijentalnoj igri madžong (od kineskog 麻將).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Mahjongg är ett roligt brädspel som är skapat baserat på det berömda orientaliska spelet Mahjong (från kinesiskans 麻將).</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KMahjongg — це захоплива гра на дошці, створена на основі відомої східної гри у маджонґ (китайською 麻將).</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKMahjongg is a fun board game created after the famous oriental game of Mahjong (from Chinese 麻將).xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KMahjongg 是一个来源于东方游戏“麻将”的有趣棋牌游戏。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">KMahjongg 是中國麻將變化出來的一種遊戲。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://games.kde.org/game.php?game=kmahjongg</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kmahjongg</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdegames/kmahjongg/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kmahjongg.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kmahjongg</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
